http://www.lionbrewery.com/privacy-policy

PRODUCTSLionshead Deluxe PilsnerLionshead LightLionshead IPALionshead Belgian WhiteLionshead DIPALionshead PumpkinStegmaier Gold MedalStegmaier IPAStegmaier OktoberfestStegmaier PumpkinStegmaier Winter WarmerStegmaier Grand HoppaLionshead Root BeerABOUTABOUT USNEWSCONTACTEVENTSSHOPShop Beer – Beverages 2UShop Beer – GoPuffSHOP MERCHANDISECONTRACTBREWINGFIND MYBEER © 2019 The Lion Brewery All rights reserved. Site byHalibut Blue®
PRIVACY POLICYYour privacy is critically important to us.Effective Date: November 25, 2019The Lion Brewery is located at:The Lion Brewery 700 N Pennsylvania Ave Wilkes-Barre, PA 18705 United States 570-823-8801It is The Lion Brewery’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.lionbrewery.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://www.lionbrewery.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, The Lion Brewery collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The Lion Brewery’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how The Lion Brewery’s visitors use its website. From time to time, The Lion Brewery may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.The Lion Brewery also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.lionbrewery.com blog posts. The Lion Brewery only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to The Lion Brewery’s websites choose to interact with The Lion Brewery in ways that require The Lion Brewery to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that The Lion Brewery gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.lionbrewery.com to provide a username and email address.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.AdvertisementsAds appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by The Lion Brewery and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.Links To External SitesOur Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.Aggregated StatisticsThe Lion Brewery may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. The Lion Brewery may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, The Lion Brewery does not disclose your personally-identifying information.CookiesTo enrich and perfect your online experience, The Lion Brewery uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Lion Brewery uses cookies to help The Lion Brewery identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.lionbrewery.com, and their website access preferences. The Lion Brewery visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using The Lion Brewery’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of The Lion Brewery’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to The Lion Brewery’s use of cookies.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, The Lion Brewery may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in The Lion Brewery’s sole discretion. The Lion Brewery encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
©2018 Lion Brewery. All rights reserved. Site by Halibut Blue® | Privacy Policy
Verify Your Age Month 123456789101112
Day 12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031
Year 19011902190319041905190619071908190919101911191219131914191519161917191819191920192119221923192419251926192719281929193019311932193319341935193619371938193919401941194219431944194519461947194819491950195119521953195419551956195719581959196019611962196319641965196619671968196919701971197219731974197519761977197819791980198119821983198419851986198719881989199019911992199319941995199619971998199920002001200220032004200520062007200820092010201120122013201420152016201720182019
Enter
